[
	{
		"question": "What was the name of the Bumblebee in the Hobbit’s Base",
		"answers": ["Honey", "Fuzzy Buzzy", "Wattpad", "It was unnamed", "There was no bee"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the first music disc the hobbits receive",
		"answers": ["Otherside", "13", "Creator", "Creator (music box)", "Precipe"],
		"correct_answer_index": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "How many kids did Helium have?",
		"answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "none"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What did Gucci do to make melon mad?",
		"answers": ["Kill his dog", "Burn his house down", "Stomp on his crops", "Flip his trap doors", "Steal from him"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Who here didn’t have a skin made by melon in season 1",
		"answers": ["Melon", "Stormi", "Classic", "Miss", "Dio"],
		"correct_answer_index": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Who got the boogeyman on the final session but never killed anyone",
		"answers": ["Kawaii", "Stormi", "Dio", "Ayra", "There was no boogeyman"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the type of arrow that Scorch used to kill Kharlie and Gucci (3rd to 2nd life)",
		"answers": ["Healing", "Poison", "Harming", "Weakness", "No potion effect"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these people did not have a custom green skin in session 1",
		"answers": ["Kawaii", "Kharlie", "Melon", "Archie", "Dio"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Classic’s Bat at the start of Double Trouble",
		"answers": ["Vincent", "Jerome", "Zoey", "Martyn", "Marucice"],
		"correct_answer_index": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of Kawaiitron’s dogs was slain by Vi in Double Trouble",
		"answers": ["Basil", "Mary", "Boxing Pad", "Punching Bag", "Sunny"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these did Kawaii not say in Double Trouble",
		"answers": ["I did an Illegal thing", "Commit a homicide", "Suction noises", "My ping sucks balls", "Sex achievement"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of these were not on Melon's red skin in Double Trouble",
		"answers": ["Burnt Leaves", "Lady Bug", "Pink Flower", "Muddy Feet", "Painted on Target"],
		"correct_answer_index": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which game took the final 2 30 minutes of time to set up and not finish",
		"answers": ["Squid Game", "Scissors, Paper, Rock", "Chess", "Checkers", "Build Battle"],
		"correct_answer_index": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Who spawned on the Snow Biome",
		"answers": ["Gucci", "Nuggie", "Dio", "Kharlie", "Ayra"],
		"correct_answer_index": 0
	}
]